MY ROYAL NEMESIS
Hello?
Where's Shin Seo-ri? Is she with you?
Wait, didn't she go to see you?
They said she left
after her boyfriend called.
-Who said that?
-It wasn't a crew member.
I think it was an extra.
Damn it.
Shin Seo-ri.
Shin Seo-ri, wake up.
Shin Seo-ri!
You're okay.
Shin Seo-ri, look at me.
I'm right here.
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to…
What am I supposed to do?
What do you want from me?
EPISODE 12
RECLAIMING LOST TIME
She's on her way home?
I mean…
Hello?
You couldn't tell me any sooner?
Got me running around in circles.
GONG TAE-WOO AND HAN MIN-HUI EXPECTING
Damn it.
Gong Tae-woo, that bastard.
So much for "anti-marriage."
It hasn't even been two months
since we broke up.
And you got her pregnant?
Ji-hyo.
What?
You have a morning shoot tomorrow.
You shouldn't be doing all this right now.
Baek Gwang-nam?
Shouldn't you be following Shin Seo-ri?
How did you end up here?
Did you put a GPS on me?
You're a celebrity, so act like one.
Have some composure.
Maintain some basic etiquette.
Etiquette, my ass.
Why don't you show some?
I mean, if you're a manager,
you should act like one.
You always talk back.
What, are you…
rich or something?
What are you talking about? Jeez.
Why did you take your socks off?
Gong Tae-woo, I hope you go bald.
Shiny bald head.
Ji-hyo, please get up. Come on.
Let go.
Go sleep at home. Get up. Please.
I live here.
Let me take you home.
I told you I'm buying today.
-Who are you?
-Jeez.
-Hold on.
-Wrong room, I guess.
-Wait.
-What are you doing?
-Wasn't that Yoon Ji-hyo just now?
-Get off. That hurts!
What would Yoon Ji-hyo be doing here?
Who are you? Please leave. Get out.
He said it's not her.
You must've seen wrong.
-It was her.
-Get out.
-Why would Yoon Ji-hyo be here?
-Hey, let go!
-No, babe. It's not her.
-Get off me!
Wake up, Shin Seo-ri.
We're here.
Already?
This is not my house.
Yeah, it's my house.
You're not going anywhere alone today.
Resistance is futile.
It is practically the size of a field.
It would take three days and nights
just to roll across from here to there.
Don't exaggerate.
Namsan Tower looks so huge.
Cha Se-gye,
you have really made it in the world.
It was not all bluff.
But you are destitute now.
Then will this house be seized soon?
Seized? No way.
Who cares if you have
that view of Namsan Tower?
When only a rocky road awaits you.
Who knows when this will be seized?
Might as well take it all in
while I still can.
You're treating me
like I'm some dirt-poor pauper.
So pretty.
Look at it sparkle.
I didn't mean for the invite
to be so slapdash.
But just so you know,
you're the first woman I've brought home.
Think of this as your own home
and make yourself comfortable--
I am already comfortable.
Why would I not be?
Oh, you're already comfortable.
Quick to adapt, as expected.
Right, I am going to lie down
and relax for a bit.
Maybe that's a bit too relaxed?
It's just the two of us here.
Hey.
Well…
Go lie down in the bedroom.
The bed there is plusher
and more comfortable.
Cha Se-gye.
I may have followed you in
because I did not have
the energy to argue with you,
but my heart has yet to give you
consent to go that far.
I see.
Turns out the struggle continues.
Help me!
Help…
What was that?
A childhood memory
from the master of this body?
When your vital energy returns,
it will guide Your Highness's soul.
Is this body already preparing itself
to welcome back its master?
Could that be why dormant memories stir?
What?
Mommy!
-Consent or not, I don't care.
-Hey, Cha Se-gye!
Cha Se-gye.
Cha Se-gye!
I'm doing this day in and day out,
and I can't even make minimum wage.
When, oh when, will I ever
Escape these streets
I'm not asking for a luxury high-rise
Just spare me the monthly room rental life
What is your name?
My name is Dan-sim.
Kang Dan-sim.
Oh my.
Goodness.
What's this now?
Seriously?
Even my hwagyeong has been awakened now?
Jeez.
Stop staring.
A demon has entered your eyes.
Go away, demon.
Shoo.
Talking nonsense again.
You must be feeling better.
Don't worry tonight and get some sleep.
I'll take care of everything tomorrow.
You always say that.
Try finding a man in Korea
more capable than me.
This isn't me talking big. This is a fact.
If you are so capable,
how did you end up destitute?
I'll turn that around too.
I totally blindsided Choi Mun-do today.
You should've seen the look on his face.
No, scrap that. You'll ruin your eyes.
You know, I've been feeling good recently.
Everything hit the fan…
but strangely, I feel good.
Maybe it's because you're by my side?
In hindsight…
I think I needed something to hold on to.
Money, honor,
status.
Things like that.
I had to hold on to something
to feel like I was alive.
Running like a car without brakes,
it felt like I was speeding
through the void.
But after aimlessly drifting,
going nowhere,
and crashing hard, I finally get it.
What's really important.
What I truly need.
I just…
I just need you.
Still, having nothing at all just isn't
a good look for a man.
Just wait a little bit.
Watch me make it back to the top.
Get your hopes up, Shin Seo-ri.
How is the Chairman doing?
He's the same. Still unconscious.
No major changes in vital signs.
I'll contact you immediately
if anything changes.
Actually, you should come right now.
Doctor!
I see.
PRODIGAL SON RETURNS TO CHAIL
If the witness isn't cooperating,
it might be better to issue
an official summons first.
Buy us some time to replace
the head of the resort TF team.
I understand. I'll have it issued
and summon him this week.
All right.
I'm told the Chairman has just woken up.
Seo-ri.
My sweet girl.
Cha Se-gye?
Where are you?
Did you leave?
MY AMAZING FAN
You're awake?
Let's make breakfast.
When did you put this on me?
Who gave you permission?
Well? Do you like it?
Is this some sort of leash?
Hey, who calls that a leash?
Just give it back then.
Who said I did not like it?
Why are you making such a fuss
about breakfast?
I'm a good cook.
My nickname when I studied abroad
was Jang-geum.
Cha Jang-geum.
You said you were Jang-geum,
but I do not see it at all.
For breakfast, you need some hot soup
to warm your stomach.
What is this? It is all dried up.
I knew you'd say that,
so I prepared something else.
How's that for a plot twist?
That's soup from the best restaurant
within the Four Gates.
Ridiculous.
Pretty.
It looks good on you.
I bought this and kept waiting
for the right time to give it to you.
Today's timing was perfect.
When did you even buy this?
Now I feel bad.
I have not really done anything for you.
Seriously? Are you looking down
on my token?
Things have been
pretty tough for me lately.
Little things like that give me comfort.
I've been taking
that herbal tonic regularly too.
Thanks to you, I'm getting both
mental and physical care.
Come on.
If you really feel that bad about it,
I'll give you a chance to make up for it.
I'll look forward to our 100th day.
What?
Were you not planning to celebrate it?
That's hurtful.
So, what should we do for our 100th?
That was just a joke.
Just let me know.
I'll prepare everything.
Our 100th day?
Well, you know…
That sort of stuff
used to make me cringe too.
But I thought I'd try it out with you.
What?
Too cheesy?
Is it too childish
if we're not in middle school?
But I…
want to try all of it with you.
Such a fool.
I do not want to lose you.
I want to keep seeing you.
Could you keep smiling like that
even if you knew I would disappear?
CHIEF OF STAFF SON JAE-HAN
Give me a second.
-When?
-Yes.
He woke up at dawn yesterday
and fell back asleep.
He's undergoing
a thorough examination right now.
But why is the hospital
only telling us now?
All right. Have the car ready immediately.
Even today, the ill-omened star
hangs in the Seoul sky.
It appears this red comet,
which had been adorning the Seoul sky
for over three months,
is about to set off on a long journey.
In about 15 days,
it will leave Earth's orbit
and vanish once more
into the unknown darkness
of the far side of the universe.
Vanish into the darkness…
It's a relief
that the Chairman woke up, isn't it?
Yes, it is a relief.
Still, it's comforting to know
that he has you by his side
at a time like this.
He has changed a lot, thanks to you.
He almost seems human now.
He may come across as prickly,
but inside he's really not like that.
He may look thick-skinned
after all that criticism,
but no one ever truly grows numb to that.
He's probably just pretending.
Right.
Never truly numb.
Father!
-Father!
-I thought you were dying.
Do you even know
-how devastated I was?
-Father.
That hurts, you brat!
Good grief. Did you forget
you're built like a mountain?
Our father is back.
That's our father all right.
Just look at that fiery temper.
All his mental faculties
are as sharp as ever.
All the test results came back clear.
Thank goodness for that.
Everyone was so worried
because you wouldn't wake up.
Hey, Choi Mun-do.
Look at you slapping on
your second face for Father.
Father, don't believe a word
this punk Choi Mun-do says.
If you only knew
the wicked things he did
while you were lying in that bed…
Are you talking
about his interim CEO appointment?
You're already all caught up.
You're finished now.
Mun-do went behind our backs
and got every single executive
in his pocket.
How else could he have gotten that
railroaded through
with a majority that fast?
Now that Father is up and about,
you better not argue and step down
from the CEO position immediately.
Don't let things get ugly.
Why would he? If anything,
it should get ugly for you two.
If you two hadn't made
such a mess of things,
maybe the board wouldn't have
skipped over my own children
to appoint Mun-do as the interim CEO.
You remain clueless
about your own shortcomings,
yet you corner Mun-do!
Father!
You need to listen to me.
You can't trust this punk.
This whole situation right now
was orchestrated by Choi Mun-do.
That's enough!
I can't believe I must claim
you two imbeciles as my children.
My goodness.
Grandfather.
Se-gye, you're here.
Se-gye, you should say
something to Grandfather too.
Yeah, Se-gye.
This is your chance to tell him in detail
about all the atrocious things
that punk has done--
When it comes to atrocities,
he's the worst offender.
What? Carcinogens?
Were you so blinded by money
that you sold your conscience?
Even when they all called you
a money-grubber,
I just let it go.
After acting like you're better
than everybody else and walking out,
this is the best you could do?
This seedy little scheme?
Without Mun-do's investment,
you'd have fallen flat on your face, punk!
None of you are qualified
to be CEO or President.
Get out of my sight, the whole lot of you.
Still, I thought blood would run
thicker than water.
Who knew he relied
on Mun-do that much?
Se-gye,
why didn't you speak up in there?
You should've said something.
I guess he has a conscience.
Se-gye, you should know
we were unjustly dragged down
by your sinking ship.
Is Grandfather really okay?
Sensory reactions are normal again,
and the swelling
in the brain has gone down.
What about
the aftereffects you mentioned?
There's a temporary memory gap
of about two weeks before the accident.
But he's recovering well,
so let's keep an eye on it.
Okay.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Mun-do,
you've been through a lot.
Thanks to you, the company survived.
Not at all, Uncle.
You should also make peace
with the rest of the family.
And give Se-gye a chance
to make things right.
He must have developed
business acumen through his startup.
I'm sure he'll really prove
himself this time.
Yes, sure.
You're absolutely right.
Interim guardian?
Yes.
Your cousin wanted us to contact
the family after daybreak.
And he requested that family visits
be restricted for the time being.
-Unbelievable.
-Though mild,
he is still suffering from aftereffects.
Absolute rest
is the top priority right now,
and as his attending physician,
I am of the same opinion.
How diligent you are,
Choi Mun-do.
FORTUNE TELLING
Why do you look so miserable?
Your Highness, you see…
Your hwagyeong has been awakened? Now?
I know I may look spiritually powerful,
like I could perform a mighty sword dance,
but the truth is,
I'm a sham shaman.
No matter how much I trained
since I was young,
my spiritual eye wouldn't open.
The only thing
that got sharper was my tongue.
I never in a million years imagined
that would suddenly awaken at this age.
For one, you do not look
that spiritually powerful.
Right.
But if you are this faint-hearted…
Your hwagyeong has been awakened,
and you have found your voice.
You will soon be channeling spirits.
Well, for now,
I can only see Your Highness.
It's tolerable for the time being.
You can see me?
Yes.
You were back in Joseon.
You said your name was Kang Dan-sim.
Kang Dan-sim.
I came clutching at straws.
But I am to leave?
So I must have seen
her childhood for a reason.
Her childhood?
I believe it is a childhood memory
of this body's master.
Tangled memories.
Phantom voices out of the blue.
That must mean…
the body's master is on her way back?
That would make sense
if her soul were still alive in Joseon.
But there's no way of knowing.
Who knows if her soul is alive or dead?
She is alive.
My body remains in a deathly trance
back in Joseon.
I see.
That body would not be alive
if it had no soul inside it.
Yes, sure.
You're absolutely right.
Are you insane?
Interim guardian?
Why? This shouldn't come as a surprise.
Uncle trusts me above all,
even bypassing his own immediate family.
Why the sudden fit,
like you had no idea?
That mouth of yours has no lid.
It's time to start minding
that tongue of yours.
Media exposure is
only going to increase from here.
The official Songjin Resort
meeting this week.
Will you be attending?
Of course.
I'm in charge of it.
Why wouldn't I be there?
Yeah, okay.
I'll see you at the meeting then.
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
You were back in Joseon.
You said your name was Kang Dan-sim.
That seals it.
Hey, Rooftop!
Where have you been?
Your place right now…
DIE
When did this happen?
This wasn't here yesterday.
When I came out to shoo away
the birds that kept pooping,
I found it like this.
Maybe there's a curse on the building?
First, the lightbulbs broke,
and now there's graffiti.
The way I see it,
this wasn't done by one of our residents.
It's definitely an outsider's doing.
I should talk to the landlord about this.
Maybe I should request
a door lock for the main entrance?
That will never happen.
Have I been
under surveillance all along?
What? Surveillance?
By who?
DAEBAK BOARDING HOUSE
SPRAY PAINT
This is truly sinister.
What did they even use?
It's not even coming off.
My poor back!
I told you to leave the heavy stuff.
Back injuries are no joke.
We have to move this quickly
so we can sleep. I'm exhausted.
That's why you should move tomorrow.
Why move in the middle of the night?
Would you be able to sleep here?
They even wrote "Die" on the wall.
They could easily bring
a sword to my throat at night.
What if I get unlucky
and end up with a scar?
I am a celebrity, after all.
You go to extremes in everything you do.
You overthink.
Is that why you're an actor?
Stop.
You better watch your mouth.
-What?
-You better not breathe a word
about what happened today
to Cha Se-gye.
I do not want him worried for no reason.
How are single people supposed to cope?
Living in this dirty hell of couples.
I heard Chairman Cha woke up.
-Have you visited?
-No.
Not yet. I had some things to sort out.
Good. I looked into it,
and I hear Chairman Cha is dealing
with some post-accident complications.
Something's not right over there.
I think it'd be best
to wrap it all up now.
That's not what I meant
when I said "sort out."
Really? Then what did you mean?
Mom, do you remember?
Ye-jin, who tutored me
in my senior year of high school.
She attended a top university
despite her poor background.
You used to praise her a lot.
I went to the department store
with a friend after finals,
and I saw her there.
She walked by
while affectionately holding Dad's hand.
When I saw her the next day,
I slapped her, and then she told me
that you knew everything.
That you even paid her
to get lost at the right time.
That's enough.
Between the two of you,
I understood you even less.
Why do you live like that?
How are you okay
with just holding on to an empty shell?
But you know what's funny?
I think I'm starting to understand
why you lived like a fool all these years.
Why you foolishly held on
and couldn't let go.
Grandfather, I'm here.
Gosh. You're here.
I bought some fruit.
My goodness.
-Did you even have time to eat today?
-No.
I haven't yet.
I don't want to let go.
It's so annoying.
It is like reaching for tears
and getting a slap on the face.
This is actually for the better.
It is a good chance
to sort out my next move.
In about 15 days,
it will leave Earth's orbit
and vanish once more
into the unknown darkness
of the far side of the universe.
Fifteen days.
So, what should we do for our 100th day?
Let me know
so I can prepare everything again.
Our 100th day?
Our 100th day will be in the spring
when flowers bloom, right?
Then let us go see
the cornelian cherry flowers.
We can make
some flower pancakes with the flowers.
-Flower pancakes?
-Yeah.
And in the summer,
we can plant trumpet vines in the yard.
Or we can go to the sea
for the beach roses.
Are you possessed
by a flower spirit or something?
You want to see every flower there is.
In the fall, we have to make
flower crowns with chrysanthemums,
so we should plant some in the yard too.
Right?
Don't kid yourself.
That's not you.
You're just a fake.
Get out of my body.
Seo-ri, my sweet girl.
Don't kid yourself. That's not you.
I know.
I do…
I must not dare to hope.
CHA SE-GYE
The caller you are trying
to reach is unavailable…
MISSED CALL
CHA SE-GYE
Call me when you see this.
I'll be waiting.
CHA SE-GYE: CALL ME WHEN YOU SEE THIS
If I leave without a word,
you will also end up waiting for me.
YEONGHWI CHAMBER
Foolishly, just like I had,
you will wait endlessly
as you wither away.
Word has come that the Grand Prince
has breathed his last in exile.
To make sure you smile
when you think of me,
just as I picture you smiling
when I miss you.
I shall convey this heart in full
and hold nothing back.
So you will not wither away alone.
Right.
This is not the time for tears.
CHA SE-GYE
Hello?
Cha Se-gye, it is I, Shin Seo-ri.
Is Grandfather okay?
He's fine, of course.
He's full of energy.
He was worried about you,
but I told him you were perfectly fine.
He asked that you visit soon.
He asked for me?
Then, before that,
should we maybe
go somewhere nice tomorrow?
-Somewhere nice?
-You know,
we have not been on a proper date yet.
Last time, we only went
where I wanted to go.
So this time,
let us go where you want to go.
I shall follow you anywhere.
Who knows where I might take you?
So bold.
Anyway,
let us go somewhere tomorrow.
Take the night to think about where.
Hello?
Jeez.
So aggressive.
I was planning to steal you away.
How could you beat me to it?
Was I sleepwalking?
How do you like your hair today?
I tried extra hard today.
Give it here.
Charity events
call for that wholesome look.
Yeah.
Like this.
Yeah? Done.
-You can go.
-Okay.
So your fling with Gong Tae-woo
was really just a rumor.
I thought Han Min-hui was fake,
and you were the real deal.
I thought you two were secretly dating
since filming that movie.
Are you nuts? Why would I date
a thug like Gong Tae-woo?
And I really don't like younger guys.
Really?
Hey, if you don't like younger guys,
how about a half-celebrity?
Shin Seo-ri's manager.
You guys looked good together.
Are you insane?
Half-celebrity? Please.
Even if he has some money,
a manager is still a manager.
-Is he well off?
-What do his parents do?
-What neighborhood?
-Well,
I heard they run a business or something.
I said no.
Why would I take over that business?
I thought this was settled.
He always has his nose up in the air.
He'll never be a manager
with that attitude.
I said no.
I will never take over
Father's department store.
Jeez.
"Department store"?
But a department store in the countryside?
It's probably just a bit bigger
than a neighborhood supermarket?
You don't know anything.
Department stores in the countryside
are where it's at.
They literally rake in the money.
Yeah, a cousin of mine
married the son of Gumi Department Store.
She's totally set for life now.
She rides supercars every day,
swapping them by color.
Shin Seo-ri, that sly fox.
She's been sitting on that golden ticket?
I told you no.
I'm not doing it. I won't.
This punk always hangs up on me.
Ma'am, how much is this?
Didn't you see our sign?
Everything here is a thousand won.
THOUSAND WON DEPARTMENT STORE
Hey, Mr. Department Store is here.
What are you guys doing?
I thought you didn't like it,
but you're wearing it.
When did I say I did not like it?
I just called it a leash.
But where are we going right now?
Should I have packed an overnight bag?
Who's the devilish one now?
After a night at my place,
an overnight trip is nothing now?
What are you talking about?
We'll have to save
the overnight for next time.
Just think of today as meeting the family.
Meeting the family?
We're on our way to see my mom.
REST IN PEACE, HAN HYE-SEON
Well?
-Isn't my mom beautiful?
-Yeah.
Incredibly beautiful and elegant.
I never understood why guys
wanted their families
to meet their girlfriends,
but now I do.
I wanted to show you off.
My pretty girlfriend.
You should have told me beforehand.
I would have dressed up nicer.
You're perfect.
How much nicer could you look?
Are you trying to show my mom up?
Mom has something to say. Hold on.
She says she's prettier.
She says not to worry.
This is the last place I came
with Mom when I was little.
Looking at it now, it's so tiny.
Why did you never come back as an adult?
Worried you might think of her?
No.
I was afraid I'd get weak.
Thinking of Mom just makes me
feel some kind of way.
It brings me down sometimes.
Mom was pretty sick when I was young.
But she lied to me.
She said she'd get healthy
and come back for me.
She told me to wait.
Se-gye.
Cha Se-gye.
Come here, Se-gye.
My dear Se-gye.
Just wait a little bit.
I'll come back for you.
I only realized much later
that she couldn't come for me.
But I didn't know that at the time.
I just sat by that window,
waiting for her every day.
Before waiting some more.
Would it have been better
if I'd known the truth?
I don't even know anymore.
I think knowing the truth is better.
-What?
-Because waiting without knowing the end…
is just too hard.
Cha Se-gye.
I do not want to lie to you.
I do not want to make you wait endlessly.
That is why I am telling you this.
I am going back.
Going back?
I have to go back
to where I came from.
So let us do everything we can,
starting today.
One by one, so we do not have regrets.
What is this?
Are you making fun of me?
I believed all this nonsense
about reincarnation
and transcending time and space,
and now you're leaving?
You're just going to leave?
Cha Se-gye.
At least try to make some sense.
If you're leaving, when are you going?
In a month? Two months?
-That is--
-Why? Is there no deadline?
Haven't you set a date?
I am not sure either.
Probably around two weeks.
-I guess there is one.
-I know this is hard for you.
I know it very well.
That is why I'm not hiding it
and telling you the truth for your sake.
For my sake?
So you asked me out on a date today
to tell me that nonsense?
You…
Do you think…
it is easy for me to tell you this?
Then what do you want? Applause?
Should I get you a palanquin
so you can return in glory?
What did you possibly expect from me
when you came to me with such nonsense?
-You…
-Why mess with me like this
if you were just going to leave anyway?
You turned someone barely holding it
together into a lovesick moron.
Right now, I…
No, you can't go.
I refuse, so just know that.
Cha Se-gye.
No.
I'm the crazy one for believing
everything you said until now.
We're going to see a doctor tomorrow.
We'll get an EEG or whatever.
Just get a full checkup,
and then we can talk.
This is just…
Damn it.
I do not want to leave either.
I want to stay by your side.
MY AMAZING FAN
If only I could take it with me.
Then I would have something to look at
from time to time.
From now on, I want all the money
coming to me to be deposited here.
Please.
NAM OK-SUN
SONGJIN GENERAL HOSPITAL
Are you going somewhere?
Now that the drama is over,
are you going on a trip or something?
A trip?
Actually, I'm glad you're here today.
You should have this picture.
Picture?
I found it while cleaning the storage.
I'll pay you back soon.
Seo-ri, my dearest daughter.
When you wake up from your nap,
we should be home.
I was right.
That was a childhood memory.
Do you remember?
She will be back soon.
Once I am gone.
My name is Dan-sim.
Kang Dan-sim.
That tone…
What is your name?
My name is Dan-sim.
Kang Dan-sim.
Just as I thought. Her tone…
I don't think it's Her Highness.
Maybe she's not going back?
Here is our next story.
According to the BBC,
five Joseon-era artifacts
currently held at the British Museum
are set to be repatriated.
Among the items to be returned
is reportedly a diary belonging
to Grand Prince Cheongheon,
the younger brother of Anjong of Joseon,
who is also known
as the "ill-fated prince."
The diary is currently…
How does it feel to be heading
into the heart of the enemy?
-…a painting of a court lady…
-For a formal meeting and not an ambush.
No reason to fuss.
When did feelings get in the way of work?
…lending weight
to the academic hypothesis.
Step on it.
Choi Mun-do must be
waiting anxiously for us.
I would like to thank
all the executives for attending
the first official meeting
for Songjin Resort today.
The fact that you took time
out of your busy schedules
shows that you support this project
and believe this will bring forth
a new era for Chail.
I appreciate it greatly.
Now, shall we begin the meeting?
Wow…
They're ostracizing me now.
Ms. Nam Ok-sun's bills are fully paid.
She's registered for automatic payments
under Mr. Cha Se-gye.
We actually needed
her guardian's consent anyway.
You can do it now.
Then this too.
Have this account be linked as well.
So she can be well taken care of
even if you cannot reach me.
Please.
She's registered for automatic payments
under Mr. Cha Se-gye.
Why mess with me like this
if you were just going to leave anyway?
You turned someone barely holding it
together into a lovesick moron.
Right now, I…
You jerk.
How could you say that?
Then again, I am the worst one of all.
Saying goodbye with a smile…
I am one greedy wench.
She is not in her room.
The patient is missing!
No need to panic.
She didn't disappear. She just went
for a short walk right out front.
Ma'am, do you have a moment?
You should speak to her doctor.
Why are you out in the cold?
What if you catch a cold?
It's fun sitting here like this.
Watching people get on and off the bus
keeps me from getting bored.
Why?
Do you like seeing people out and about?
No, it's not that.
Actually…
my dream when I was a kid
was to be a driver.
Other kids wanted to be the bus guides.
But I really wanted to be the driver.
Gosh. Driving all day in a car,
having a blast,
making money, and seeing the world
to my heart's content.
Living life on your own terms is enviable.
I was so envious of that.
A little disappointed I couldn't.
Now, the next item on the agenda
is the most important issue.
Securing the site.
Earlier at the groundbreaking ceremony,
press releases went out saying
the site was fully secured,
but the plot near the resort entrance
hasn't been purchased yet.
The site purchase needs to be completed
before construction begins,
but the owner of this plot
is very stubborn.
You don't worry about that.
The head of our new TF team
will take care of it.
Isn't that right, Mr. Cha?
What?
I guess it hasn't been shared
with the executives yet.
Thanks to Mr. Cha Se-gye's connections,
we have successfully signed
a contract with the restaurant owner.
SEORI'S NOODLE SHOP
Thanks to the legwork he put in,
we have finally secured 100% of the site.
Please give him a round of applause.
That's a good age.
But they don't know that.
-I'll have tteokbokki.
-Let's add one serving of beef brisket.
I thought I'd be
young like that forever too.
But I blinked, and I became an old lady.
I was so busy rolling all that dough.
I didn't know my hair had gone gray.
But still,
that doesn't mean
I didn't like running the restaurant.
Watching kids enjoy my noodles
made me full too.
That's why I didn't stop working.
But now,
that's all over too.
I should slowly start wrapping things up.
Is it because
of the restaurant demolition?
I will try to take care of that--
No, look at me.
How do I look to you?
Do you think I can run a restaurant again?
Ms. Nam Ok-sun is not doing well.
While we couldn't reach you,
her cognitive function
has dropped rapidly.
As well as her physical function.
You should probably prepare yourself…
Prepare myself?
She doesn't have much time left.
Of course you can. Why not?
No.
I only held on to it all this time
out of greed and sentiment.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
Hey, it's cold out today.
Why are you wearing such thin clothes?
Your hands are so cold. Jeez.
My granddaughter
always goes around with her hands
freezing like this too.
In a little bit,
the sun will set.
She's late.
Miss, you must be cold.
Here. Put this on, at least. Go on.
Here you go.
I'll lend it to you until my bus comes.
My granddaughter bought this for me.
How is it?
Doesn't it feel a bit better wrapped up
all warm and cozy like this?
It's pretty.
No, I am…
I am not…
Miss, why are you crying?
Are you upset about something?
Oh my. You'll lose your energy
if you cry like this.
Please don't cry.
What's wrong with me?
Why does my chest hurt so much?
Don't cry, okay?
Don't cry…
It hurts.
Don't cry.
You can't go in right now…
So this is what you wanted?
You just wanted me to walk out on my own?
No, why would you leave?
I already told the Chairman
to watch closely as you prove yourself
with the chance you were given.
To see
what our Crown Prince chooses.
What?
I guess you don't know this yet,
but I'm more compassionate than I look.
Look at me right now.
I'm giving you a chance
to regain Uncle's trust.
And also a chance
to win love.
Whatever you do, you'll gain something.
Is there a reason to be this mad at me?
Look at you having a blast.
Your eyes light up
when you play with people.
Yeah, I'll admit it.
It is fun.
But you should probably hurry up now.
If you decide to choose her,
you don't have much time left.
What time?
The demolition team should be heading
to the site right now.
They'll arrive before sunset.
I told them to demolish
the entrance plot first.
To wipe out
that messy commercial area first.
Well?
Shouldn't you go and check on her?
You bastard.
There we go.
This is the Cha Se-gye I know.
Throwing punches without thinking
and cursing up a storm.
Only knowing how to throw a tantrum.
You really
have never wanted for anything.
Just a kid running wild
without knowing how the world works.
Fine.
Do whatever you want.
Do whatever you want with the company.
Tear it apart or destroy it.
But that messy restaurant spot
isn't important at all.
You can easily just leave it alone.
I haven't done a single thing right
for that woman.
So just leave that alone.
Is that an order?
Or a favor?
Pick one.
If you step on me, I'll let you.
If you tell me to bow, I will.
So just let that one thing go.
To us, it may be a messy,
insignificant restaurant,
but for someone else,
it's their home and their life.
So just spare them that.
I'm begging you.
I thought you were a kid,
but you're a man.
Now we can finally talk.
Right?
But you know what, Se-gye?
I gave the demolition team
special instructions.
No matter who, no matter when…
No matter what happens,
they are to proceed.
Too bad.
Damn it.
Damn child.
Director Jang.
Please follow me.
Jang Seok-ho!
Your Highness!
-Excuse me.
-Where did she go?
-What are you doing there?
-Her Highness.
No, I mean. Where did Seo-ri go?
She went to see her grandmother. Why?
I need to tell her this.
I need to let her know
as soon as possible.
Why isn't she picking up her damn phone?
What are you talking about?
You can tell me.
No. It's--
I'm her manager.
Just tell me.
SEORI'S NOODLE SHOP
2025 TO 2026
So meticulous.
You know, I've been feeling good recently.
Everything hit the fan,
but strangely, I feel good.
You idiot.
I think I needed something to hold on to.
I had to hold on to something
to feel like I was alive.
All caught up in your own damn feelings.
I finally get it.
What's really important.
What I truly need.
You don't know anything.
I just…
I just need you.
I was completely oblivious to the despair
you've shouldered alone.
It's not cabbage. It's basically gold now.
It's so ridiculous.
I might just start farming it myself.
The sign across the street says
they're the original.
The original kalguksu?
They're making me laugh nonstop.
Half of this is just swearing.
Such a foul mouth she has.
Oh my, that little brat.
When I told her to eat some carrots,
she threw a fit and pinched me.
For a little thing,
she's got a strong grip.
Grandma, I'm home.
My sweet girl. You're home.
-Let's eat some carrots!
-What?
-I said no!
-I don't want to!
-Come on!
I hate carrots.
That hurts! You little brat.
My goodness.
My Seo-ri is on TV.
I was so excited that I gave
everything away for free today.
Look at my sweet girl.
I'm so glad Dong-seok took her to Seoul.
He should have taken her sooner.
My Seo-ri is on every time
I turn on the TV.
I mean, I'm happy about it,
but is she doing okay in school?
Is she eating well?
I'm worried because
she's as skinny as a skewer.
I miss you.
2002 TO 2003
Her belly is cold.
I'm worried because
she always has a stomachache.
I should brew
some herbal medicine for her.
Grandma.
My tummy aches. Can I have a tummy rub?
Do you have a stomachache again?
Come here.
Oh my.
Grandma will give you her healing hands.
Grandma's hands are healing hands
Seo-ri's tummy is a potbelly
Hey! I don't have a potbelly!
Grandma's hands are healing hands
Seo-ri's tummy is a potbelly
What is this?
They told me to wait.
They said they'd be right back.
They told me to wait here.
What is wrong with me?
But that's quite strange.
Childhood memories
should have been borne away
with the soul of the body's master.
How did they stay and get tangled up?
Why do I keep…
Right. This is not my body,
and those are not my memories.
How did they get tangled with my own?
I was just trapped again.
I was trapped.
It felt like I was dying.
The soul and memories are a pair.
They shouldn't be separated.
It feels like they are mine.
How does that make sense?
How?
Seo-ri.
My sweet girl.
When are you coming?
When is my sweet girl coming?
Seo-ri.
My sweet girl.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Seo-ri, my sweet girl.
Grandma!
-Grandma, I'll be taller than you!
-Yeah.
Okay, let's make sure!
My sweet girl.
This is crazy!
Really?
My sweet girl. How exciting!
My sweet girl.
Grandma.
That's not you.
You're just a fake.
Get out of my body.
No, I am not a fake.
I am…
My name is…
Shin Seo-ri.
Just a little bit.
Just wait a little bit longer.
MY ROYAL NEMESIS
I'm not letting you go anywhere.
I am not going back.
Because I have returned to where I belong.
I'll put the brakes
on the resort development.
I hear they're building an airport
next to the resort site.
-What about Seo-jun?
-Your driver picked him up.
Your threat was loud and clear.
And you crossed a line you shouldn't have.
Her condition has rapidly deteriorated.
Grandma.
Tell me.
I will pay any price!
Even at the cost
of never returning here again?
Subtitle translation by Justin S. Kim